CALLUM BECKWITH

PERSONAL PROFILE:

I have a Bachelor of Science with First Class Honours in Computer Science and currently, work as a Senior Software Developer for Audit Partnership. Within this role, I build and maintain data-heavy software used to audit some of the largest companies in the UK and USA. I am responsible for multiple team members and provide them with the programming and company knowledge necessary to develop their skills. Prior to working in the finance sector, I ran a freelance design and development partnership, where I produced branding, marketing, and online software solutions for a wide range of clients.

I can programme in several languages and effectively utilise frameworks, as well as familiarise myself with most development stacks. I am accustomed to the agile development methodology, frequently lead sprints, and have responsibility for the distribution and reviewing of developers' work. I have been involved in the recruitment preparation for technical interview processes of prospective employees, as well as collaborating with the new members to support their integration into the team. I am also proficient with various development environments and have modest experience with design software.

EDUCATION:

Sheffield Hallam University BSc Computer Science First Class Honours

Sept 2017 - Sept 2021

New College Pontefract

A Levels: Maths, Economics and ITC

Sept 2014 - Jun 2016

Kettlethorpe High School

10 GCSE passes A - C

Sept 2009 - Jun 2014

REFERENCES:

Douglas Muzawazi

Student's Union Manager Sheffield Hallam Students Union

Adam Everington

IT Manager Audit Partnership Ltd

(Contact Details Available on Request)

Telephone:

07403333115

Email:

123callumb@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE:

Senior Software Developer Audit Partnership Ltd

Jun 2019 - Present

Q York, UK - Remote

Full stack software developer working with large client datasets - skills include .Net Core/Framework, Node.Js, C#, TypeScript, JavaScript, SQL, SCSS, Bundling, Azure, Azure Dev Ops, Agile, Scrum.

Freelance Web Designer and Developer Webur

Jun 2018 - Present

Sheffield, UK

Duties include handling clients, producing company branding, site designs and full stack web development - skills include PHP, React.JS, Node.Js and more...

Junior Web Developer Sheffield Hallam Students Union

Jun 2018 - Sept 2018

Sheffield, UK

Duties include the creation of multiple web pages (including designs), a blog system and a Welcome Week page.

Web Application Developer Liberty Trading GB Ltd

Apr 2017 - Sept 2017

Parnsley, UK

Duties include handling stock values across three companies and developing private inventory analysis software.

Non-tech industry experience

Waiter
Wetherby Whaler

Jun 2016 - Sept 2016

♀ Wakefield, UK

Conference and Banqueting Cedar Court Hotel Wakefield

iii Nov 2014 - Jan 2016

Wakefield, UK

INTERESTS/ACHIEVEMENTS:

As a representative for Sheffield Hallam University our team placed 2nd in a Hackathon hosted by Kyocera Documents and Solutions.

My hobbies focus on music, I am able to play the guitar (self - taught) and currently teach myself the piano whilst exploring music theory.